{
    "quizzes": {
        "802619144460566577": {
            "abc": [
                {
                    "question": "a b c",
                    "answers": [
                        "a"
                    ]
                },
                {
                    "question": "a b",
                    "answers": [
                        "a"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ],
            "new quiz": [
                {
                    "question": "Who does the quick brown fox jump over?",
                    "answers": [
                        "Jacob",
                        "The lazy dog",
                        "My calculator",
                        "62"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "q 2",
                    "answers": [
                        "a 2.1",
                        "2.2",
                        "2.3"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "q 3",
                    "answers": [
                        "a 3.1",
                        "a 3.2",
                        "a 3.3"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "q 4",
                    "answers": [
                        "a 4.1",
                        "a 4.2",
                        "a 4.3"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "q 5",
                    "answers": [
                        "a 5.1",
                        "a 5.2",
                        "a 5.3"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ],
            "new quiz 2": [],
            "mmmm": [],
            "wacky quiz": [
                {
                    "question": "Who does the quick brown fox jump over?",
                    "answers": [
                        "Jacob",
                        "My calculator",
                        "62",
                        "The lazy dog"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                },
                {
                    "question": "Square root of 4.",
                    "answers": [
                        "One",
                        "Two",
                        "Three",
                        "Four"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is my favorite color?",
                    "answers": [
                        "Red",
                        "Green",
                        "Blue"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ],
            "What is the last digit of pi?": [
                {
                    "question": "0",
                    "answers": [
                        "a"
                    ]
                }
            ]
        },
        "815510544189882418": {
            "qaz": [
                {
                    "question": "Is Hyrum sus",
                    "answers": [
                        "yes",
                        "no"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ],
            "quiz 2": [
                {
                    "question": "Square root of 4.",
                    "answers": [
                        "One",
                        "Two",
                        "Three",
                        "Four"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Question 2",
                    "answers": [
                        "2?",
                        "WRONG"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    },
    "users": {
        "270957488038346752": {
            "lastguild": "802619144460566577",
            "lastquiz": "quiz 2"
        },
        "210567192524095490": {
            "lastguild": "802619144460566577",
            "lastquiz": "wacky quiz"
        },
        "406256627763773441": {
            "lastguild": "802619144460566577",
            "lastquiz": "What is the last digit of pi?"
        }
    }
}